<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Staying up later than I should</title>
    <link>https://notes.beakstar.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Staying up later than I should</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 23:55:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://notes.beakstar.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How this site was built</title>
      <link>https://notes.beakstar.com/posts/how-this-site-was-built/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 23:55:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://notes.beakstar.com/posts/how-this-site-was-built/</guid>
      <description>Modern tools can make building a website or blog quite easy and painless, especially if you&amp;rsquo;re willing to accept the out-of-the-box templates and setup. However, when you start wanting things &amp;ldquo;just so,&amp;rdquo; the process becomes a little more complicated.
Technologies in Play For the live site, we have:
Github Pages Giscus That&amp;rsquo;s it. It&amp;rsquo;s a static site published to a Github repository with Github Pages enabled. The post comments are powered by Giscus , an application that integrates with Github Discussions on the repository.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where Are My GitHub Pages?</title>
      <link>https://notes.beakstar.com/posts/where-are-my-github-pages/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 10:57:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://notes.beakstar.com/posts/where-are-my-github-pages/</guid>
      <description>This site runs on GitHub Pages, and while it&amp;rsquo;s a great feature, it was initially a bit confusing to understand where everything should be.
There are three main types of GitHub Pages:
GitHub Pages for a GitHub user GitHub Pages for a GitHub organization GitHub Pages for a specific repo GitHub Pages for a GitHub User or Organization Consider this the primary &amp;ldquo;site&amp;rdquo; for an account. GitHub Pages for an account (or organization) is a general site not tied to a specific repository.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Go head, tailor your tools</title>
      <link>https://notes.beakstar.com/posts/tailor-your-tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 22:42:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://notes.beakstar.com/posts/tailor-your-tools/</guid>
      <description>I recently heard someone else share their perspective that one should not customize their tools. I also fell into this camp, until pretty recently.
The lesson of vi I made what I believed was a wise choice back in the 90s when I was first getting comfortable in unix (AIX at the time). I decided to eschew other options and learn and stick with vi, at least for editing system configuration files.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
